(忆往昔)
小卡跟克劳力搭伙了
Cass is chumming it up with Crowley.
他们在一起追踪路西法
They're hunting Lucifer together.
是啊  一个天使  一个恶魔
That's right -- one's an angel, one's a demon,
还一起破案
and apparently, they solve crimes.
路西法现在是烂摇滚大师
So Lucifer is now the Master of Butt Rock.
他跳进了文斯·文森特的身体
He jumped into Vince Vincente.
-那个摇滚明星  -混蛋差不多
- The rock star? - The douchebag.
他以前留长紫发及腚
Guy used to roll with purple hair down to his butt
还穿带尖刺的护挡
and a spiked codpiece.
-那是80年代嘛  -你还替他说话
- It was the '80s. - What, are you defending him?
不是  他第三张专辑还挺...
No. I mean, his third album was kind of...
-不那么差劲  -我现在恨死你了
- not horrible. - I hate you so much right now.
我见识过文斯的各种样子
I'v'een around all stripes of Vince, all right?
醉酒的文斯  抑郁的文斯
Drunk Vince, depressed Vince,
夸大狂的"我是金上帝"的文斯
megalomaniacal "I'm a Golden God" Vince.
但把我从门里丢出去的文斯
The Vince who threw me through that door...
那不是他
that wasn't him.
如果你有他的消息  一定给我来电
If you hear from him, don't hesitate to call.
好的...碧昂斯探员
Okay, Agent...Beyoncé.
这么跳皮囊我都腻了
This vessel hopping's getting old.
我刚习惯了一具肉身的限制
Just as I get used to the limitations of one meatsack,
就得弃船  再跳进另一具不完美的身体里
I gotta cut bait and jump to the next flawed lump.
你是要我把这具皮囊弄成永久性的吗
Then you want me to make this vessel permanent?
足够强大  能支撑住你
Strong enough to hold you?
是挺合适我的
Does look good on me.
[咒语]
小红  你做了什么
Red, what did you do?
加速了腐败  陛下
Sped up the decaying process, my Lord.
红发贱人
Ginger bitch!
你休想毁掉我
You can't destroy me!
现在还不行  但我可以送你去很远的地方
Not yet, but I can send you far, far away.
去海底找新皮囊吧
Try finding a new vessel at the bottom of the bloody ocean.
[咒语]
(如今)
-黑暗领主  -恶魔
- Dark Lord. - Apollyon.
魔王
Beelzebub.
作为您卑微的仆人  我们恳求您
As your humble servants, we beseech thee.
我们呼唤您的名字  召唤您
We say your names as summonings.
现身吧
Show thyself!
-毒蛇  -魔鬼
- Serpent. - Devil.
路西法  现身吧
Lucifer! Show thyself!
让我沐浴于您的荣光
Rain your splendor upon me.
用您罪恶的愤怒滋润我
Let me bathe in your unholy wrath.
浸湿我吧  路西法
Drench me, Lucifer.
别闹了  科迪
Cut it out, Gordy.
哥们  这不好笑
Dude, it's not funny.
哥们  你让路西法"浸湿"你
Dude, you asked Lucifer to drench you.
又不是我写的
I didn't write it, okay?
是美国撒旦崇拜者协会认证的召唤文
It's a Satanist Society of America-approved summoning.
我在网上查到的
I found it online.
是啊  还有那件"宝物"
Yeah, like you found that "artifact."
承认吧  亚当  你的"撒旦羽毛"
Face it, Adam, your "Satan feather,"
比我继母从唐人街买来的包包还山寨
is faker than my stepmom's Chinatown Fendi.
-是真的  -就是块石头
- It's real. - It's a rock.
石化了  这是路西法翅膀的羽毛
Well, it's fossilized. A feather from Lucifer's wing.
卖家是从他的一个地宫中挖掘出来的
The seller excavated it from one of his crypts.
路西法还有"地宫"
Lucifer has "crypts."
路西法还有"翅膀"
Lucifer has "wings."
你蠢死了
You're so frickin' dumb.
其实
Actually...
我一直在找那个
I've been looking for that.
不可能
No way!
绝不可能
No freakin' --
你好
Hiya.
你是...
You're...
成功了  我的召唤...
I-it worked! My summoning actually --
"召唤"了我的  是这个
The only thing that "summoned" me was this.
这具皮囊已经不行了
This vessel was already wearing out,
我的海底之旅更是帮了倒忙
and my trip under the sea did not help.
补充一点能量
With a little power up...
坚持不了多久  但也能凑合了
Won't last long, but it'll do.
你和你的...伙计
So, uh, you and your...pal,
你们是我如今典型的人间追随者吗
are you typical of my following on Earth these days?
因为...
'Cause...
不不不  你不可能是路西法
No, no, no, no, no, no. You can't be Lucifer.
你是文斯·文森特  我妈可喜欢你了
You're Vince Vincente. My mom loves you.
你...还算有名
You're...kinda famous.
还算有名
Kinda famous.
[邪恶力量 第12季第7集]
"电臀舞"  瞧好吧
"Twerking." Booyah.
(这哪叫词)
(自己查字典)
不是吧
Seriously?
怎么了
What?
我一直在查英国记录者的资料
So I've been trying to dig up info on the British Men of Letters,
留意是否有案件出现
keeping an eye out for cases,
而你则游手好闲
and you've been goofing off
玩一个五年前就不流行了的游戏
with a game that went out of style five years ago?
我觉得妈妈还没准备好玩阅后即焚呢
I don't think Mom's quite ready for Snapchat.
-你在跟妈妈对战  -是啊
- You're playing against Mom? - Yeah.
就是一个月前还不知道
The same Mom that didn't know
电话是什么物的妈妈
what a cellphone was a month ago?
是啊
Yeah.
不太公平吧
Doesn't exactly seem like a fair fight.
(超级词)
你刚说什么来着
You were saying?
她最近如何了
So how she been lately?
挺好的  她还在应对
She's good. You know, she -- she's dealing.
(小卡)
小卡
Hey, Cass.
迪恩
Hello, Dean.
你还在跟克劳力演80年代兄弟喜剧吗
You still living out an '80s buddy comedy with Crowley?
很遗憾是的
Unfortunately.
有路西法的消息吗
Any news on Lucifer?
有的  看新闻
Actually, yes. Look at the news.
(搜索提示  文斯·文森特)
稍等
One sec.
(黑暗领主  重金属新闻  美女心:微金属不死)
(美女心与死亡警报唱片签约)
不会吧
No way.
这是今天的新闻
So this is from today.
我们站在死亡警报唱片门前
We're here in front of DeathSiren Records...
-不可能  -采访文斯·文森特
- Oh, no friggin' way. - ...with Vince Vincente.
是的  很高兴能够重组乐队
Yes, it's, uh, it's great having the band back together again.
在录音棚里  精神百倍
In the studio, feeling pumped.
好久没这么有劲了
Haven't felt this fired up in ages.
很多人认为  你的摇滚风格
A lot of people saying that your style of rock
在当今的气候下是不可能东山再起的
could never make a comeback in today's landscape.
你要怎么说
What do you say to them?
下地狱去吧
Go to hell.
-告诉我那不是路西法  -我们不确定
- Tell me that's not Lucifer. - We don't know.
小卡  你不是说罗威娜伤到了他吗
Cass, I-I thought you said Rowena got some licks in.
他这会儿不该把皮囊用坏了吗
Shouldn't he have burned through his vessel by now?
是啊  但我们不确定...
Yeah, but we don't know. We don't --
好啊  小子们  好久没见
Hello, boys. Long time.
我们组队救世界来着  然后就没然后了
We team up to save the world, and then bupkis.
你们不打电话  不写信
You don't call, you don't write.
-我们不在乎  -克劳力  路西法呢
- Yeah, we don't care. - Crowley -- Lucifer.
路西法  想想看
Lucifer. Think about it.
那么多消亡的摇滚乐队
Of all the extinct rock acts,
美女心是最古旧的
Ladyheart are the most Paleolithic.
如今  2016年
A major label
会有大唱片公司复活这帮恐龙
sponsored comeback in 2016 for those dinosaurs?
感觉不太自然  是吧
It doesn't feel like a wholly natural turn of events, does it?
或许路西法想到了办法治愈他的皮囊
Maybe Lucifer found a way to heal his vessel.
但是...搞什么啊
Yeah, but still... I mean, what the hell?
他在洛杉矶  我们那里见
He's in L.A. I'll see you there.
洛杉矶
Oh, L.A.
嗯
Yeah.
你去哪
Where are you going?
我认识个人
I know a guy.
(好莱坞)
(贝弗利山)
(死亡警报唱片)
你好  罗素
Hello, Russell.
克劳力兄弟
Brother Crowley.
稍等  我收个尾  很快的
One moment. Just let me tie this off real quick.
好了
All right!
那么
So...
你为何会来到天使之城
what brings you to the City of... Angels?
你清楚这是我的城市
You know this is my city.
你搞这套精神领袖的破玩意做什么
What's with all this Maharishi crap?
我去年搬去了西区
I moved to the Westside last year.
开始每日冥想  做瑜伽  喝绿色果汁
Started daily meditation, yoga, green juice.
能帮我克制自大  和愤怒
Helps to keep the ego and the anger in check.
不说我了  你最近如何
But enough about me. How you been?
健康  家庭
Health? Family?
地狱
Hell?
无所谓  不在乎  不如往日
Doesn't matter, don't care, and been better.
好消息
Well, good news. Good news.
我有几个不错的新秀给你
I got a couple of quality up-and-comers for you.
渴求成功的年轻才俊  唾手可得的灵魂
Thirsty young talent. Souls ripe for the taking.
你还满意我们的...安排吧
You have been pleased with our...arrangement so far?
非常满意
As punch.
灵魂就是灵魂
A soul's a soul.
但是能拥有一个斯威夫特
But there is a certain prestige
或德雷克是挺长脸的
to owning a Swift or a Drake.
喜欢吗
You like that?
德瑞博士给的
It's a gift from Dre.
文斯·文森特回归的事
This whole Vince Vincente comeback thing...
-是开玩笑的吧  -不是
- It's a joke, right? - No.
非常认真的  朋友
Deadly serious, my friend.
其他的过去都能被我们
We've raided, repackaged, and resold
拿来  重包装  再出售
everything else from our past.
为什么不能给微金属个第二次机会
Why not give hair metal another shot?
好吧  我也是有怀疑的
Yeah, okay. I doubted it, too,
但文斯向我提出了一个很棒的提议
but Vince came to me with a killer pitch.
把最初的美女心成员重新召集起来
The original Ladyheart lineup reunited.
想当年  他们卖过一千万呢
Back in the day, those cats sold, like, 10 mil.
胡蒂与河豚也辉煌过
So did Hootie & the Blowfish.
我也会让他们回归的
And I'll bring them back, too.
我知道美女心可能会成为笑柄
I know Ladyheart might be a punch line,
但他们乐队的认知率爆表
but the band's got off-the-chart name recognition.
而且光是跟文斯谈话
And just talking to Vince,
他感觉不一样了
he seemed different, you know?
很有精神  重焕生机
Energized. Reborn.
容光焕发
Lit.
就像个全新的人
Like a whole new man.
是啊
Exactly.
好了  离洛杉矶还有450英里
All right. 450 miles to L.A.
到处交通堵塞  遍地肉毒素
Land of gridlock, Botox,
征税过重  眼高手低
overtaxing, underachieving,
汗味和绝望臭气熏天
smell of sweaty desperation.
无法呼吸  海滩有毒
I mean, you can't breathe. The beaches are toxic.
还有穿瘦腿牛仔裤  在室内戴墨镜的傻逼
You got dudes in skinny jeans wearing sunglasses inside.
和痴迷于形象的自恋狂
Image-obsessed narcissists.
但我喜欢瑜伽裤
I do like the yoga pants, though.
我们多久没去过洛杉矶了
When was the last time we were in L.A.?
10年前  杀复仇鬼的时候吧
About 10 years ago, doing a vengeful spirit?
感觉像是过了一辈子  是吧
Man, that seems like forever ago. Doesn't it?
跟你说话呢
Tryin' to talk to you here.
-什么  -你
- What? - You...
你听什么呢
What are you listenin' to?
播客  怎么了
Uh, podcast. Why?
好吧
All right, well...
我需要点东西保持清醒  放大声点
I need something to keep me awake, so crank it up.
是历史主题的播客
I mean, it's a history podcast.
我喜欢历史
Well, I like history, you know?
角斗士  法外之徒  海盗
Gladiators and outlaws, pirates.
我们开的就是件历史遗物
Hell, we're driving a piece of history right here.
不是那种历史
N-not that kind of history.
这是...
This is a, uh...
是关于宗教改革历史的播客
it's a podcast on the history of the Protestant Reformation.
分部探究
A multipart exploration
讨论马丁·路德的95篇论文
of each of Martin Luther's 95 theses.
是啊  我也觉得你不会喜欢
Yeah, that's what I thought.
-萨姆  -哥们
- Sam. - Dude.
微摇滚  不是吧
Hair rock? Really?
-不是微...  -拜托
- It's not hair - Come on.
不是微摇滚  迪恩  是重摇滚
It's not hair rock, Dean. It's hard rock.
是真真正正的重摇滚
It's legitimate hard rock.
人不可貌相  海水不可斗量
Don't judge a book by its cover.
是啊  不能看到彩虹假发和豹纹就对人妄下结论
Yeah, or a dude by his, uh, rainbow wig and leopard prints.
彩虹假发  什么
Rainbow wig? What?
告诉你  我不想再道歉了
You know what? I'm done apologizing.
路西法附身了文斯·文森特
Lucifer possessed Vince Vincente.
这是文斯·文森特的音乐  听这个也算调研
This is Vince Vincente's music, so listening to it is research.
-不  不  -事实上
- No. No. - As a matter of fact...
研究一下吧  迪恩
Study up, Dean.
不  不
No, no. No.
我不想听
I don't wanna listen to it.
-你喜欢的  -不不  不
- You like it. - No. No. No, no. No.
关掉
Turn it off.
你会喜欢上的
It'll grow on ya.
(死亡警报录音棚)
你关于美女心回归的推文
Your tweet about Ladyheart's reunion
已经有一百万多条转发了
already has over a million engagements.
你独唱时  有300个点赞就不错了
When you were solo, you were lucky to have 300 "likes."
乐队在音乐云上发布的前瞻音频
The band's teaser track on SoundCloud?
4小时内有50万的点播量
500K streams in 4 hours.
消息网刚发了个榜单
Buzzfeed just posted a listicle --
"关于美女心你需要知道的10件事"
"10 Things You Need to Know About Ladyheart."
这很棒  文斯  非常好
This is good, Vince. This is really good.
-太好了  -要成了  文斯
- Great. - It's happening, Vince.
我们又要名声大振了
I mean, we are gonna be famous again.
文斯
Vince.
我们还录不录音了
So, we actually gonna record or what?
没太有感觉
Not really feelin' it.
拜托  哥们
Come on, man.
乐队已经重组了
The band's back together.
我们有录音的预算
We've got an actual recording budget.
哥们  我们来制作音乐吧
Dude... let's make some music.
音乐
Music.
粉丝们现在在说我什么
What are the fans saying about me right now?
他们在就你昨晚跟帕米·安德森吃饭的事发推
They're tweeting about your drinks with Pam Anderson last night,
猜测你俩是不是要旧情复燃
speculating if you two are rekindling.
他们还在争论文斯·文森特
And they're debating whether Vince Vincente
是帅  恶  还是老了
is bae, nay, or daddy.
那是什么意思啊
What the hell does that even mean?
意思是  音乐不是重点
It means it's not about the music.
从来都不是
It never really was.
摇滚并不是原因  只是个借口
You know, rock's not the reason. It's just an excuse...
让人崇拜  爱慕
to worship, to adore.
瞧  人类一直都需要
See, humans have always been desperate
把什么人或什么东西置于他们之上
to put someone or something above them.
承认吧  如今  上帝已经不够格了
And let's face it, God ain't cuttin' it these days.
得要金·卡戴珊
It takes a Kim Kardashian,
或是贾斯汀·比伯那种的才行
a whatever Justin Bieber is.
像我这种的
A me.
他们享受这份快乐
They're enjoying the ride.
你也该如此
So should you.
(贝拉克酒店)
怎么了
What?
这很好的
It's good.
是蔬菜水
It's vegetable water.
萨姆  迪恩
Sam, Dean.
你要不要换身衣服
You consider switching up your duds there?
在这儿显得太老土了
Bit stiff for this town.
他可以是个探员之类的
He could be an agent or something.
三流探员吧
Yeah, maybe a third-tier agent.
至少我不会像个伐木工
At least I don't look like a lumberjack.
够了  你俩  克劳力呢
Okay, enough. Guys, where's Crowley?
他说会在这儿碰面的
He said he'd meet us here.
老实说  能跟他分开一会儿也好
Frankly, I appreciate the break.
好几周了  他一直就在我旁边
It's been weeks, and he's been right there,
念叨个不停
just talking and talking and talking.
无休无止
It's relentless.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
毛毛和我都难舍难分了
Feathers and I are all but inseparable now.
-你有发现吗  -有
- You find anything? - Yes.
文斯·文森特被魔鬼附身了
Vince Vincente is riding with the Devil.
好吧  那现在怎么办
Okay, so what now?
我建议去他房间看看
I suggest we go check out his room.
按计划  文斯今天会一直在录音棚
Vince is scheduled to be in the studio all day,
-我们没问题  -钥匙卡哪来的
- so we're covered. - How'd you get the card?
这里是洛杉矶  我认识很多人
This is L.A. I know a lot of people.
看来是发生过打斗
Well, looks like there was some kind of a fight.
是啊  打得挺投入
Yeah. Some kind.
看啊
Look at this.
摇滚歌星自传  都集齐了
Rock star biographies. Like, all of them,
从史密斯飞船到ZZ托普
from Aerosmith to ZZ Top.
他好像在学习如何出名
It's like he's studying how to become famous.
怎么  路西法成书呆子了
Well, so what, Lucifer's a dork?
好啊
That's good to know.
看啊  "成熟火龙果的种子
Look at this -- "The seeds of a ripe dragon fruit
滴上1盎司的槐花蜜
drizzled with exactly 1 ounce of Acacia honey,
放在陶瓷碗里  塑料不行"
prepared in a ceramic bowl -- no plastic."
这是什么咒语
What is this spell?
是早餐  是文斯的附加条款
It's breakfast. It's Vince's rider.
-我见过更麻烦的  -我不懂
- I've seen worse. - I don't get it.
路西法此刻可以去接管天堂和地狱
Lucifer could be taking over Heaven and Hell right now,
结果  他却在这里实现摇滚之王的幻想
and instead, he's trying to act out some rock god fantasy?
是啊  换谁不会啊
Yeah. Who wouldn't?
我有发现
I found something.
那是什么
What is that?
似乎是人的牙
It appears to be a human tooth
连牙根拽下来的
pulled out by the root.
能问你件事吗
Can I ask you something?
你为什么跟我待在一起
Why are you spending time with me?
你那么多年来一直无视我
You ignored me for years,
我倒不是怪你
not that I blamed you.
是我太傻
I was a fool
没有看清你的痴心
not to recognize such sweet devotion.
跟我说说  萝丝琳
Talk to me, Roseleen.
跟我说说
Tell me about...
我
me.
你是文斯
You're Vince.
文斯·文森特
Vince Vincente.
我从见到你的一刻就知道自己爱上了你
And I knew I was in love with you the moment I saw you.
我那时才16  就是阿卡迪亚一个普通少女
I was 16, just a normal kid growing up in Arcadia.
阿卡迪亚  好美的名字
Arcadia. Sounds beautiful.
我当时在看《重金属爱好者舞会》
I was watching "Headbanger's Ball"
上面播了《血腥弥赛亚》的MV
and the "Bloody Messiah" video came on.
我...
And I...
你的声音
It was your voice.
你的头发  你的眼睛
And your hair. And your eyes.
你的一切
It was everything.
你就是一切
You were everything.
就算人们取笑我
And even when people made fun of me --
单位比我小的女生
younger girls at work,
取笑我的美人心文身
shredding on my Ladyheart tattoos
说你是个笑话
and saying you're a joke --
我从未停止爱你
I never stopped loving you.
也永远不会
And I never will.
你有多爱我
How much do you love me?
你愿做什么来表达你的爱
What would you do to show me?
任何事
Anything.
任何事吗
Anything?
你愿流血吗
Would you bleed?
那就流血吧
Then bleed.
格林菲尔德太太流血过多
Mrs. Greenfield has lost a lot of blood
伤疤也不可治愈  但她稳定下来了
and there'll be no fixing those scars, but she's stable.
她自残的吗
And she cut herself?
她将他的名字刻在了胸膛上
She carved his name into her chest.
"文斯·文森特"  一个字没漏
"Vince Vincente." Didn't skip a letter.
而且割得很深
And she cut deep.
谢谢  医生
Thanks, Doctor.
还是那句  搞什么鬼
Well, again, what the hell?
-我去跟她谈谈  -不不不  你别去
- I'll go talk to her. - No. No, no, no, you won't.
小卡  待这儿  看住他
Cass, stay here. Keep an eye on him.
好吧
Well...
又一起了
together again.
真棒
Yay.
我们想搞明白发生了什么
We wanna understand what happened,
但首先  你得开口
but in order for us to do that, we need you to talk.
萝丝琳  是文斯逼你的吗
Roseleen, did Vince force you to do this?
不是
No.
文斯没有
Vince didn't.
他不用逼我
He wouldn't have to.
是我想的
I wanted to,
让他看到  哄他开心
to show him, to make him happy.
你就没想过  是什么样的变态才会
You ever stop and wonder what kind of sicko
把看着别人自残当作开心事吗
gets happy off of watching somebody melonball their own flesh?
别那么说文斯
Don't talk about Vince like that.
他有理由的  很好的理由
He had a reason, a good reason.
他肯定有
He must have.
他肯定能解释清楚一切
I'm sure he can explain everything.
如果我能见见他
If I could just see him --
我得赶去演出
I need to get to the show.
求你们
Please!
好吧  今晚的演出
Okay, we're building an aura
我们要制造神秘和秘密感
of mystery and exclusivity with tonight's show --
地点保密  观众少  有选择性
undisclosed location, small, select audience.
谁拿不到票跟谁拿得到票一样重要
It's as much about who doesn't get a ticket as who does.
这可以让你在社交网络上达到"金耶"的量级
This could push your social media profile to Kimye levels.
谁能拿到票
Who gets the tickets?
在网上抽取本地粉丝
It's an online lottery of local fans,
但会倾向于美女心的死忠粉
but it'll tend towards the Ladyheart diehards.
-他们会更关注...  -我受够死忠了
- They'll be more engaged - I've had my fill of the diehards.
他们已经很爱我了
They already love me.
宗教  名人  推特
Religion, celebrity, Twitter --
规则都是一样的
it's all the same rules.
如果你的追随者不增加  就是在减少
If you're not gaining followers, you're losing followers.
今晚我要换一群听众  新粉丝
I want a different crowd tonight. New fans.
听着  找新听众
Look, getting a new audience
对社交媒体曝光是好事
is great for social media visibility,
对总体声势也是好事
which is great for overall buzz,
但他们很善变
but they're fickle.
他们不在音乐上花钱  毫无忠心
They don't spend any money on music. They have no loyalty.
想把他们的关注转化成
Good luck translating their attention
专辑和门票的销售可不容易
to album or ticket sales.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我要新鲜血液
I want fresh blood.
懂了
Got it.
表演就在今晚
So the show is tonight?
她是这么说的
That's what she said.
路西法会唱歌  或演奏乐器吗
Can Lucifer even sing or play an instrument?
我看笼子里不会有吉他入门教程
I doubt they offer Intro to Guitar in the cage.
那才不重要  路西法逼那女人做的事
Like it matters. What Lucifer made that woman do
跟音乐毫无关系
has got nothing to do with music.
-是为了忠心  -什么
- It's about devotion. - Come again?
你们这些渺小的人不会理解
You little people wouldn't undend,
但我当过国王
but I've been a king.
有人把你当作一切
Having people look at you like you're everything,
一旦他们信奉了你
knowing that once they buy in,
你就可以让他们做任何事
you can make them do anything,
那感觉令人陶醉
it's intoxicating.
太吓人了
Well, that's super creepy.
那么这场音乐会  这些人
Okay, so this concert, all these people, what is --
-路西法想做什么  -不是好事
- what is Lucifer planning to do? - Nothing good.
-罗威娜...  -亲爱的老妈说
- Is Rowena - Dear Mother says
等我们抓到路西法  她才会现身  之前不会
that once we catch Lucifer, she'll show, no sooner.
没有罗威娜  我们武力不足
Well, without Rowena, we're outgunned.
有她  我们还是打不过他
With her, we're outgunned.
无所谓了  这是我们的机会
It doesn't matter, guys. This is our shot.
我们得查明他今晚在哪里演出
We just gotta find out where he's playing tonight.
我们开工吧
All right, let's get to work.
连我也不知道
A mystery to even me.
但即便我知道  我大概也不会告诉你
Though, even if I did know, I probably wouldn't tell you.
你甘愿拿我们利润颇丰的合作冒险
You'd threaten our very lucrative partnership
维护一个过了气  染发失败的摇滚恐龙
for one over-the-hill, bad dye job rock dinosaur?
文斯是棵摇钱树  哥们
I'm smelling money with Vince, bruh.
这是生意  克劳力  不必往心里去
This is business, Crowley. It's nothing personal.
相信我
No, believe me,
我很往心里去
it's personal.
(死亡警报录音棚)
汤米
Tommy.
我们里面见
Guys, I'll meet you inside.
探员  你怎么来了
Agent. What are you doing here, man?
调查文斯  跟之前一样
Investigating Vince, same as before.
你听说萝丝琳的事了吗
You hear what happened to Roseleen?
是啊  那事很糟糕
Yeah, that was, uh, it was awful.
但是...她自残的  是吧
But, I mean, come on, man, she cut herself, right?
-又不是  -你清楚事情没那么简单
- It wasn't like... - You know that's not the whole truth.
你知道文斯已经不是文斯了
You know Vince isn't Vince.
我们是摇滚兄弟
We're the brothers that rock together.
就像美国的绿洲乐队
We're kind of like the American Oasis.
但是用合成乐器
But with synths.
-是啊  所以我们很潮的  -是啊
- Yeah, right, so, you know, we're -- we're hip. - Exactly.
-谁弹什么  -我弹键盘
- Who plays what? - I'm on keys.
-他是鼓手  -吉他
- He's on the drums. - ‭Guitar.
打鼓和吉他  我什么都会
Drums and guitar. I pretty much do it all.
我们在网上看到你代理文斯·文森特
We saw online that you represent Vince Vincente.
我们希望你能为我们做
We were kind of hoping you could do for us
你为他做的事
what you've done for him.
抱歉
Sorry.
我同意见面只是因为你们的照片很帅
I took this meeting 'cause you looked hot in your pics,
但我对你们没什么感觉
but I am not feeling this.
告诉你吧  我们其实不是为了会面而来
Okay, you know what? We're not actually here for a meeting.
文斯今晚的表演  在哪举行
Vince's show tonight -- where is it?
你们是什么人
Who are you guys?
你肯定发现了  文斯不一样了
Look, you must've noticed, Vince is different.
我不知道
I...don't know!
你在惹地狱烈火  罗素
You're messing with hellfire, Russell.
你必须查明表演在哪举行
You will find out where that show is.
你必须告诉我
You will tell me
否则  我就灭了你
or I will end you.
布丽吉塔  再给我拿杯绿色果汁来
Brigitta, get me another green juice in here.
有礼了
Namaste.
演出在哪举行  汤米
Where's the show, Tommy?
我不知道文斯是怎么回事
Man, I don't know what the hell's going on with Vince, all right?
我们热曲的版税早就断流了
All the royalties on our hits dried up years ago.
我有两个女儿在上大学
I got two daughters in college.
我知道我看到了什么  但是
I know what I saw, but...
你不在乎谁会付出代价吗
And you don't care who pays the price?
抱歉
Sorry.
文斯让我不舒服  但他是我的雇主
Vince gives me the skeeves, but he's a playing client.
不  他是魔鬼
No, he's the Devil.
是啊  真魔鬼
Yeah, like, literally.
我是个公关
I'm in P.R.
我服务过性别歧视者  种族歧视者  甚至政客
I've worked for sexists, racists, even politicians.
我的工作就是把魔鬼打造成圣徒
My job is making saints out of devils.
我绝不会损害他的利益
No way I'm threatening my reputation
败坏我自己的名声
by working against his interests.
你们得离我远远的  否则我就大叫
So you need to take a step back or I start screaming. And
在这样人流熙攘的地方
in a crowded place like this?
我这样的妹子  你们这样的汉子
Girl like me, two guys like you...
猜猜结果会怎么样
Guess what happens next?
再见了
Buh-bye.
(贝拉克酒店)
你说你吓住罗素了
And you said you put the fear in Russell.
我觉得是的
I thought I had.
那些瑜伽疯啊
These yoga types.
你以为已经震慑住他们了...
Just when you think you've harshed their mellow...
我在网上到处查
Yeah, well, I've been looking everywhere online,
没有人知道在哪
and, uh... no one's linked the venue yet.
-不是吧  -怎么了
- Seriously? - ‭What?
-哥  -闭嘴
- Dude. ‭- Shut up.
小卡
Cass.
有发现吗
Anything?
没有
No.
我们无法
So we couldn't flip
让文斯身边任何一个人开口
a single member of Vince's team.
哪怕有大屠杀的威胁
Even with the threat of mass murder,
这些南加州的二逼也不肯做正确的事
these SoCal douchebags won't do the right thing.
这就是洛杉矶
Welcome to Los Angeles.
现在怎么办
So what happens now?
我从没见过这么多哭泣表情
I've never seen so many crying emojis in my life.
那些没票的人
The people who didn't get in,
都在推特上哭爹喊娘
they're rending garments all over Twitter.
八卦博客  社交媒体
Gossip blogs, social media,
都在热烈猜测秘密重聚表演
they're on fire speculating about the secret reunion show.
-得票的呢  -激动死了
- And the winners? - ‭Thrilled.
如果有新音乐可推出他们会更激动
Be more thrilled if we had new music to sell.
什么
What?
文斯没去录音棚
Vince was a no-show at the studio.
又没去
Again.
缪斯
The muse --
大概是去洗手间了
guess she took a powder.
放松  罗素
Relax, Russell.
今晚的表演
Tonight's show?
会大杀四方的
It's gonna kill.
我在你身上冒了险  文斯
I took a chance on you, Vince.
一个老迈  早已过了巅峰期的垃圾摇滚乐手
An aging, well-past-his-prime buttrocker.
你必须听话
You will get in line.
否则呢
Or?
否则我就都收回
Or I take it all back.
看看你的合同
Check your contract for it.
你不听我的  我可以毁了美女心
You don't do what I say, I can bury Ladyheart.
你是我的
I own you.
-是吗  -是啊
- Do you? - ‭Yeah.
怎么回事
What's happening here?
-哥们  -文斯  你做什么呢
- Hey, man. - Vince, what are you doing?
哥们
Hey, man.
文斯  停下
‭Vince, stop!
文斯
‭Vince!
里面见
See you all inside.
文斯
Vince!
谁想找点乐子
Who's ready to have fun?
文斯  我爱你
Vince, I love you!
文斯
‭Vince!
谢谢
Thank you!
-我爱你  文斯  -我辞职
- I love you, Vince! - I quit.
(美女心  重聚演出)
(碧昂斯探员  演出一小时后在流星俱乐部举行)
各位
‭Guys.
汤米还是不接
Tommy's still not answering.
他让我们找到地方了  这才重要
Well, he got us here. That's what matters.
天使语手铐  你就使这招
Enochian handcuffs. That's your move?
-对付我就够  -你不是他
- They held me. - ‭You're not him.
我们无法保证什么
We have no sure bets here, okay?
我们用什么武器都会像BB弹
Anything that we use is gonna be like popping BBs.
真会鼓舞士气  加油  小队
Oh, great pep talk. Go, team.
各位  我们不仅要抓住机会对付路西法
Guys, we're here to do more than just take a shot at Lucifer.
-是吗  -是的  我们还得救里面的人
- We are? - ‭Yes, we need to save the people inside, too.
我去对付路西法  他是我的责任
I'll take Lucifer. He's my responsibility.
不是的  他是我们所有人的责任
No, he's not. He's all of our responsibility.
如果你想顺利疏散那群人
Well, the only way you'll clear that crowd without drawing fire
就得让他无暇顾及
is if he's otherwise engaged.
那让他顾及什么  小卡  杀你吗
Engaged in what, Cass? Killing you?
小卡  你至多能撑个三分钟
Cass, you'll last... three minutes tops.
那我就替你们拖个三分钟
Then I'll buy you three minutes.
我们需要四分钟
Make it four.
怎么了  我帮忙的
What? I help.
看到外面的人群了吗
Have you seen that crowd?
我上次见到这么激动的观众
Man, I have not seen an audience this hyped
-还是91年我们是摇滚怪兽头牌的时候  -嗯
- since we headlined Monsters of Rock in '91, man. - No.
还有迷妹们
And the girls?
正值芳龄
Perfect age.
汤米
Tommy?
你没事吧
You okay?
我们无畏的领袖
Our fearless leader.
你对演出有什么感觉  汤米
How you feelin' about the show, Tommy?
是啊  我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
好紧张
The nerves.
看来我今晚之前该练习一下的
Guess I should've practiced before tonight.
或是...有过一点练习也好
Or, you know, ever.
你是谁
Who are you?
我曾经是谁  那不重要
Who I was... well, that doesn't matter.
我现在是谁
Who I am?
我是文斯·文森特  摇滚上帝
Well, I'm Vince Vincente, rock god.
经过小心考虑
And after careful deliberation,
我决定要摆脱累赘
I've decided to cut the dead weight.
我要单飞
I'm going solo.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
你好久才来啊
Took you long enough.
其他小淘气你也带来了吗
Did you bring the rest of the Little Rascals?
就我一个
Just me.
小胖墩
Spanky.
抱歉
Sorry.
你们闻到烟味儿了吗
Hey, you guys -- you guys smell smoke?
一二三  文斯  文斯
One, two, three! Vince! Vince!
没想到你还会做个殉道士  克劳力
Did not take you for the martyr type, Crowley.
我真不是  我就是有那么恨你
I'm really not. I just hate you that much.
你是想干什么  路西法
What are you doing, Lucifer?
你对外面那些孩子来说毫无意义
You mean nothing to those kids out there.
你以为他们会为你流血吗
You think they'd draw blood for you?
自愿流血
By choice?
我觉得至少该问问
I thought I'd at least ask.
如果他们不肯自愿献出
And if they won't give it up by choice,
-那我就强夺  -为什么
- maybe I'll just take it. - ‭Why?
因为好玩
Because it's fun.
因为我能
Because I can.
因为做路西法
And because being Lucifer?
有太多基督宗教的包袱
So much Judeo-Christian baggage.
但文斯  他是个名人
But Vince? He's famous.
人人都爱他
Everybody loves him.
我需要爱
And I need love.
我的童年真的很不幸
I had a really jacked childhood.
汤米
Hey, Tommy. ‭
你觉得这好玩
You think this is fun?
我知道你不会理解的
Oh, I wouldn't expect you to understand.
我进入过你体内
I was inside you.
我知道你是个怎样无趣  只知道责任
I know what a weak, duty-bound... ‭
毫不知享乐的闷蛋
pleasureless dullard you are.
还有你
And you.
坏狗狗  坐下
Bad doggy. Sit!
不  说真的  好像有烟味儿
No, seriously, I-I-I think I smell smoke, everyone.
确定你不是中风了吗
Sure you're not having a stroke?
真的  我们得出去了
Hey, I'm serious. We need to get out of here.
别碰我  老爷子  你什么毛病
Step off, dad. What's your problem, man?
-别碰我  -我们得...
- Get off me! - We gotta --
-好了  -别让他碰我
- All right, yeah. - Get this guy off me!
-听我说  -你什么毛病
- No, listen to me, okay? Listen, - What's your problem, old man?
我们得离开这儿
we gotta get out of here.
好了
Okay. All right, yeah.
听着  我们得把大家疏散出去
Okay. Look, we gotta get everybody out of here.
那俩丫头真聪明
Clever girls.
不不不
No. No, no, no, no, no.
糟糕
Oh, no.
留下参加余兴派对
Stick around for the afterparty.
你们好  洛杉矶
Hello, L.A.!
好一群观众
What a crowd!
我爱你  文斯
I love you, Vince!
看这些新鲜的面孔
Look at all those fresh, new faces.
大家激动吗
Everyone excited?
你们是该激动
Yeah, you should be!
今晚不会是一般的演出
Tonight's not gonna be a typical show.
今晚  你们将看到前所未见的东西
Tonight, you're gonna see and feel things
感受到前所未有的感觉
you never saw or felt before.
可能会有些失控
Things might get a little bit messy.
不管了
Screw it.
-他有枪  -我们得走了
- He's got a gun! - We gotta go! We gotta go!
快走  各位
Go, go! Come on, guys!
不不不
No, no. No, no, no.
快走
Go!
Go.
混球
Hey, assbutt.
迪恩
Hi, Dean.
萨姆
Sam.
看得开心吗
Enjoy the show?
各位  你们知道我一个弹指
Guys, you know I could end you all
就能干掉你们所有人吧
with a snap of my finger?
但我为什么要那么做
Why would I do that
你们对我
when you can't do anything...
什么都做不了
...to me?
你为什么这么做
Why are you doing this?
为什么
Why?
你和上帝和好了  你原谅了他
You and God made up. You forgave him.
他会怎么想啊
What would he think?
我并不是很想知道他的看法
I'm not especially interested in his opinion.
亲爱的老爸  他终于为抛弃我道歉了
Dear old dad, he finally apologized for abandoning me.
他紧接着就做了什么呢
And what's the very next thing he does?
他抛下了我
He ditches me.
也抛下了你们
And you, too, by the way.
跟阿玛拉姑妈绝尘而去了
And rides off into the sunset with Auntie Amara.
他需要我帮助
He needed my help,
就愿说任何甜言蜜语哄我
and he'd say anything to get it.
他的话  你们的话  毫无意义
His words, your words, they mean nothing.
你还不明白吗  这一切都毫无意义
Don't you get it? This is all meaningless.
天堂  地狱
Heaven, Hell,
这个世界
this world.
如果它曾有过意义  那一刻也过去了
If it ever meant anything, that moment is past.
这里只有一群只图一时消遣的家伙
Nothing down here but a bunch of hopeless distraction addicts,
如此空虚
so filled with emptiness,so
如此渴望弥补空白
desperate to fill up the void...
他们不介意
they don't mind being served
看陈旧的翻新陈旧
another stale rerun of a rerun of a rerun.
你知道我的计划是什么吗
You know what my plan is?
我没有计划
I don't have one.
我只想继续破坏老爸已经坏掉的玩具
I'm just gonna keep on smashing Daddy's already broken toys
逼你们看着
and make you watch.
是吗
Yeah?
因为看上去  你要不行了
'Cause it kinda looks like you're falling apart.
是啊  你这里有点东西
Yeah, you got a little something, uh, right there.
承认吧  摇滚已死
I mean, face it, rock is dead.
没办法
What can I say?
揍你是很耗费体力的
Kicking your ass took a lot out of me.
别担心
But don't worry.
勇往直前
Onward and upward.
你感觉怎么样
How you feelin'?
我没死
I'm not dead.
我得承认
Well, I gotta hand it to you.
你说过会引开路西法的火力
You said you were gonna draw Lucifer's fire
还真是没少挨揍
and you drew some serious fire.
是啊  大获成功
Oh, it was a grand success.
我们没抓到路西法  但我们救了那些人
Well, we didn't catch Lucifer, but we did save the crowd,
我觉得这算赢了
so I'm gonna call that a win.
我不觉得
I wouldn't.
文斯·文森特死了
Vince Vincente is dead.
我们根本没指望能救他
We never even hoped to save him. ‭
是啊  我知道  第三张专辑
And, yes, I know, the third album --
不  他始终是个人
No, he was still a person,
而且他对很多人有些意义
and he meant something to a lot of people.
(摇滚明星文斯·文森特死亡)
路西法扭曲了那一切
And Lucifer just took all that and just twisted all that up
然后毁灭了它
and snuffed it out.
路西法有计划  有动机时就够糟了
Lucifer was bad enough when he had a plan, a motive.
现在他只是想找乐子
Now he's just having fun.
今晚死了多少人
I mean, how many people died tonight?
这一切  都是我们的责任  是我们放他出来的
Them, this, it's all on us. We let him out.
我们没有赢
We're not winning.
我们在慢慢地输
We're just losing slow.
你听到他的话了
And you heard what he said.
勇往直前  他要玩得更大
Onwards and upwards. He's gone big.
而且不会停止
And he'll go bigger.
我们会阻止他的
And we will stop him.
我们会的
We will.
这是我们的工作
It's what we do, man.